Guide to the UE News Photograph Collection, 1933-1998 UE.14.1
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Districts and Locals, 1940-1998; 14.1.2.
  - Local 750: Taylor Winfield Corp., Warren (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Local 751: General Electric, Niles (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Local 751: General Electric, Niles, 1980-1990 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Local 754: Master Electric, Dayton (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Local 755: Delco Products, Dayton (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Local 756 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Local 757: Formics Insulation, Cincinnati (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Local 758: Humphryes Mfg. Co., Mansfield (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Local 759: Mansfield (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Local 761 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Local 762: Stomdale Industries, Lima (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Local 763: St. Mary's Foundry (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Local 764: American Buildings Company, Jamestown, OH (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Local 764: American Buildings Company, Jamestown, OH, 1980-1990 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Local 765: Allis Chalmers, Norwood (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Local 765: GRH Foundry, Dayton (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Local 766: J.H. Day; Homan Electric; Wesche Electric, Cincinnati (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Local 766: National Foundry; Dayton; Ametek Westchester Plastics; Wapakonet, 1980-1990 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Local 767: Line Material Plant, Zanesville (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Local 767: Antioch (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Local 767: Antioch, 1980-1990 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Local 768 (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - Local 768: GHR; Malleable Iron, Dayton (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Local 769: General Electric, Indianapolis (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Local 776: Monarch Machine Tool Co., Sidney, OH (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Local 777: Cleveland (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - Local 793: Simpson Industries; Maumee Valley Vending; Sparta Industries, Lima and Sparta, WI (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - Local 801: Frigidaire, Dayton (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - Local 804: Leland Electric, Dayton (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - Local 807 (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - Local 236: UE-FE, Louisville, KY (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - District 7: Joint Wage Conference (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - District 7: General (Box 18, Folder 61)
  - District 7: General, 1960s (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - District 7: General, 1970s (Box 18, Folder 63)
  - District 7: General, 1980s (Box 18, Folder 64)
  - District 7: Political Action (Box 18, Folder 65)
  - Local 803: General Electric, Kansas City (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Local 805: General Electric, Tell City (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Local 809 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Local 810: St. Louis (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Local 813: Seeger; Servel, Evansville (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Local 814 and Local 819 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Local 822: Eagle Signal Corp., Moline (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Local 825: Small Arms, St. Louis (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Local 1102: St. Louis (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Local 1104: Wagner Electric, St. Louis (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Local 1110: Meissner Mfg. Co., Mt. Carmel (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Local 1116: Advertising Novelty Company, Newton (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Local 104 F: UE FE; International Harvester, Moline (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Local 109 F: UE FE; Interenational Harvester; Farmall, Rock Island, IL (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Local 111 F: UE FE; International Harvester; Rock Island, IL (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Local 115 F: UE FE; Oliver, Charles City (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Local 123 F: UE FE; French and Hecht, Davenport (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Local 150 F: UE FE; John Deere, Moline (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Local 157 F: UE FE; Internaltional Harvester, Canton (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Local 209 F: UE FE; Iowa Public Service, Waterloo (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Local 233 F: UE FE; International Harvester, Canton (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - District 8: Veterans (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - District 8: General (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Local 901: General Electric, Fort Wayne (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Local 902 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Local 903: Wayne Pump, Fort Wayne (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Local 904: American Bearing Co., Indianapolis (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Local 905: Peru, Indiana (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Local 906: Alladin Industries, Alexandria (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Local 907: Vickers Co., Detroit (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Local 910: Magnavox, Fort Wayne (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Local 912: Farnsworth, Bluffton (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Local 915: Horton Mfg., Fort Wayne (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Local 916: Farnsworth, Fort Wayne (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Local 921: Marion Machine Foundry and Supply, Marion (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Local 922 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Local 923: General Electric, Wabash (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Local 924: General Electric, Decatur, 1941-1979 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Local 924: General Electric, Decatur, 1980-1998 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Local 924: General Electric, Decatur (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Local 925: A-1 Compressor, Indianapolis (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Local 926 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Local 927: Electro Voice Co., Buchanan, MI (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Local 931: Whirlpool; Remington Rand, St. Joseph (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Local 932: Ironite: Mt. Clemens (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Local 933: Phelps Dodge, Fort Wayne (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Local 935: Detrola, Detroit (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Local 936 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Local 937: Square D, Detroit (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Local 947: Keystone Mfg., Centerline, MI (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Local 947: General Electric, Detroit (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Local 957: Square D, Detroit, 1953-1971 (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - Local 958: Automatic Sprinkler, Monroe, IN (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - Local 733: Reliance Electric and Mercury Equipment, Ashtabula (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - Local 733: EMCO Wheaton Inc., Conneaut (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - Local 743 (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - Local 1001: J.P. Mallory, Indianapolis (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - Local 1003 (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - Local 1004 (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - Local 118 F: UE FE; International Harvester, Richmond, IN (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - District 9: Fair Practices Committee (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - District 9: Wallace Material (Box 19, Folder 62)
  - District 9: General (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - Local 1002 (Box 19, Folder 64)
  - Local 1007: General Electric, San Jose (Box 19, Folder 65)
  - Local 1008: Westinghouse, Sunnyvale (Box 19, Folder 66)
  - Local 1010: General Electric, Ontario, CA (Box 19, Folder 67)
  - Local 1012: General Electric, Ontario, CA (Box 19, Folder 68)
  - Local 1013: Cannon Electric, Ontario, CA (Box 19, Folder 69)
  - Local 1014: General Cable, Sanger, CA (Box 19, Folder 70-71)
  - Local 1015: Carol Cable, Glendale, CA (Box 19, Folder 72)
  - Local 1016, Tucson, AZ (Box 19, Folder 73)
  - Local 1089: General Electric (Box 19, Folder 74)
  - Local 1090: Echlin, Friction (Box 19, Folder 75)
  - Local 1094: Warner Brothers, Hollywood (Box 19, Folder 76)
  - Local 1099: Mountain Valley Express, Sacramento (Box 19, Folder 77)
  - Local 1400 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Local 1412: Oakland, CA (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Local 1421: Los Angeles (Box 20, Folder 03-07)
  - District 10: General (Box 20, Folder 08-12)
  - Local 1103, Eau Claire, WI (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Local 1105: Westinghouse, Chicago (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Local 1109: Line Material Co., Milwaukee (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Local 1111, Milwaukee (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Local 1111: Allen Bradley, Milwaukee (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Local 1111, Milwaukee (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Local 1111: Allen Bradley, Milwaukee (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Local 1112: Badger Die Carting Co., Milwaukee (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Local 1113: Marathon Electric, Wausau, WI (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Local 1114: Honeywell (Box 21, Folder 10-11)
  - Local 1114 (Box 21, Folder 12-13)
  - Local 1115: Garton Co., Sheboygan, WI (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Local 1119: Eckay Mfg., Chicago (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Local 1121: Warwick Mfg. Co., Chicago (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Local 1122 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Local 1131: Louis Allis Co., Milwaukee (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Local 1132: Peter Cooper Co., Milwaukee (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Local 1138 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Local 1139: Butler Mfg., Minneapolis (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Local 1144: ABC Washer, Peoria (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Local 1145: Honeywell, Minneapolis (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Local 1146: Moline, Minneapolis (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Local 1149: Belmont Radio, Chicago (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Local 1150: Miehle Printing Press and Mfg., Co. (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Local 1154: Stewart Warner, Chicago (Box 21, Folder 27-28)
  - Local 1155 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Local 1169: Brass Foundry, Peoria, IL (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Local 1180: Litton (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Local 1180: Litton, Sioux Falls, SD (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Local 1181 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Local 1188: General Electric (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Local 1196: Oak Industries; Madison, WI (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Local 101 F: UE FE; International Harvester, Chicago (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Local 107 F: UE FE; International Harvester, Chicago (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Local 108 F: UE FE; International Harvester, McCormick (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Local 116 F: UE FE (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Local 128 F: UE FE (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Local 139 F: UE FE; Ingersoll Steel and Disc, Chicago (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Local 140 F: UE FE, Peoria (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Local 141 F: UE FE; Harvester Twine Mill, Chicago (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Local 151 F: UE FE; Aetna Ball and Roller Bearing Co., Chicago (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Local 161 F: UE FE; International Harvester, West Pullman (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Local 164 F: UE FE; American Brake Shoe Co., Chicago (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Local 166 F: UE FE; Polar Ware, Sheboygan, WI (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Local 167 F: UE FE; Vollrath Co., Sheboygan, WI (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Local 173 F: UE FE; Bastian Morley, LaPorte, IN (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Local 182 F: UE FE (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - Local 187 F: UE FE (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - Local 189 F: UE FE; International Molding Machine Co., Chicago (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - Local 190 F: UE FE; Phoenix Closures Inc., Chicago (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - District 11: General (Box 22, Folder 01-06)
  - Local 1199: Hospital Workers, Charleston, SC (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Local 1201: Bassick Sack Co., Winston Salem, NC (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Local 1201: Westinghouse, Tampa (Box 22, Folder 09-10)
  - Local 1202: General Electric, Charleston, SC (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Local 1204 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - District 12: General (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Founding Officers, 14.1.3.
  This series contains photographs of the founding members of the UE. Albert Fitzgerald served as the General President, Julius Emspak served as the General Secretary-Treasurer, and James Matles served as the Director of Organization.
  - Albert Fitzgerald (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - James Matles (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Julius Emspak (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Individuals and Topics, 14.1.4.
  This series contains photographs of prominent UE and non-UE individuals. Included are union officials and politicians whose actions affected the labor movement. Conference Boards, strikes, and demonstrations are also documented in this series.
  - Abbondi, Peter: Local 456 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Agler, Don (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Aguilar, Jacquelyn: Local 1012 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Aldridge, George (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Almeida, Julius (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Allen, Frank: Field Organizer (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Amelse, Joseph: Local 139 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Anderson, Andrew: Local 307 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Arias, Victor: Local 1012 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Arsenault, Oliver: Local 203 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Assetti, Thomas: International Representative (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Atkins, Judy (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Bailey, Cecil: Local 630 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Balbier, Irving: Local 240 President (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Banks, Frank: Organizer (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Barile, Pat: Local 428 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Barry, Richard: District 5 President (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Barry, Walt (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Barth, Fred (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Bell, Evelyn (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Benoit, Leonard: Local 202 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Berescik, Michael (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Berrigan, Daniel (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Bersing, Carl (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Beveridge, Campell (see also District 6) (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Bittman, John: Field Organizer (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Bloch, Ed: International Representative (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Block, Boris H. (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Block, Harry (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Brant, Carl (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Brant, Neil: International Representative (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Brantley, Pansy: Local 437 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Brashear, Dewey: Local 301 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Brooks, Ellis: Local 203 Business Agent (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Brown, John (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Brown, Robert: District 1 President (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Bruno, Edmund and Budenz, Louis (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Burch, William (Jack): Local 1119 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Burch, Dorothy: Local 732 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Burdick, Al (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Burkhart, A.L. (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Burns, Frank (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Bunting, E.G.: Local 901 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Caldicott, Helen M. (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - Calabresa, Anthony: Local 1111 (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - Callahan, John (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - Camacho, Humberto (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - Cameron, Angus (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - Cameron, Clifford (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - Carbone, Ed: Field Organizer (Box 24, Folder 50)
  - Carlucci, Ray: Labor Spy (Box 24, Folder 51)
  - Carey, James B. (Box 24, Folder 52)
  - Carter, Connie: Local 430 (Box 24, Folder 53)
  - Carter, Felicia: Local 429 (Box 24, Folder 54)
  - Cetner, Joseph: Field Organizer (Box 24, Folder 55)
  - Chandler, Marian: Local 155 (Box 24, Folder 56)
  - Chase, Dorothy: Activities Director (Box 24, Folder 57)
  - Choate, Norm (Box 24, Folder 58)
  - Christoffel, Harol (Box 24, Folder 59)
  - Ciofarri, Albert: Local 209 President (Box 24, Folder 60)
  - Clague, Ernestine (Box 24, Folder 61)
  - Clark, Robert L.: Secretary Treasurer (Box 24, Folder 62)
  - Clough, Al: Organizer (Box 24, Folder 63)
  - Cognatta, Peter: Local 301 President (Box 24, Folder 64)
  - Cole, Archer (Box 24, Folder 65)
  - Cochran, Floyd (Box 24, Folder 66)
  - Compa, Lance: Washington Representative (Box 24, Folder 67)
  - Coleman, Michael: Local 475 (Box 24, Folder 68)
  - Conroy, James (Box 24, Folder 69)
  - Conselyea, Harold: Local 410 (Box 24, Folder 70)
  - Cooper, Charles: Local 308 (Box 24, Folder 71)
  - Cook, Anthony: Local 455 (Box 24, Folder 72)
  - Cordia, Mrs. Joseph: Local 1104 (Box 24, Folder 73)
  - Corwin, Earl C.: Local 901 (Box 24, Folder 74)
  - Coulthard, Alfred: Local 201 (Box 24, Folder 75)
  - Counts, Ezra: Local 409 (Box 24, Folder 76)
  - Coville, Rose: Local 1225 (Box 24, Folder 77)
  - Criley, Florence (Box 24, Folder 78)
  - Criscuolo, Walton: Local 443 President (Box 24, Folder 79)
  - Crouch, Paul: Labor Spy (Box 24, Folder 80)
  - Cuny, Lt. Arthur: Local 408 (Box 24, Folder 81)
  - Cushing, Sidney: Local 201 (Box 24, Folder 82)
  - Cvetic, Matthew: Informer (Box 24, Folder 83)
  - Dahl, Harold: Local 907 (Box 24, Folder 84)
  - D'Allesandro, Anthony (Box 24, Folder 85)
  - Dalton, Leland: Local 139 (Box 24, Folder 86)
  - Danahy, Dorothy: Local 332 Trustee (Box 24, Folder 87)
  - Darin, Margaret: District 6 (Box 24, Folder 88)
  - Daugherty, James: Field Organizer (Box 24, Folder 89)
  - Davidson John: Local 276 President (Box 24, Folder 90)
  - Davies, T.P.: Local 524 President (Box 24, Folder 91)
  - Davis, Terry (Box 24, Folder 92)
  - Davis, David (Box 24, Folder 93)
  - Decavitch, Victor: District 7 (Box 24, Folder 94)
  - DeForrest, Chal (Box 24, Folder 95)
  - Delaney, Thomas (Box 24, Folder 96)
  - Delong, Harley: Local 209 President (Box 24, Folder 97)
  - DeMaio, Anthony (Box 24, Folder 98)
  - DeMaio, Ernest: National Vice President (Box 24, Folder 99)
  - Dermody, Joseph: International Representative (Box 24, Folder 100)
  - Devine, Joseph (Box 24, Folder 101)
  - DiBassi, Nate (Box 24, Folder 102)
  - Donner, Frank: General Counsel (Box 24, Folder 103)
  - Dorsey, Charles: Local 124 President (Box 24, Folder 104)
  - Dowling, Lyle (Box 24, Folder 105)
  - Eastman, Neal (Box 24, Folder 106)
  - Egri, James: Local 724 (Box 24, Folder 107)
  - El Conin, William (Box 24, Folder 108)
  - Emspak, Frank: Local 301 President (Box 24, Folder 109)
  - Emspak, Julius (see Founding Officer file) (Box 24, Folder 110)
  - Essin, Michael (Box 24, Folder 111)
  - Fagechagh, Ole: Field Organizer (Box 24, Folder 112)
  - Fancher, Linda (Box 24, Folder 113)
  - Fay, Charles: Local 475 President (Box 24, Folder 114)
  - Felsen, Milton (Box 24, Folder 115)
  - Fielde, Gerald (Box 24, Folder 116)
  - Fiering, Claria (Box 24, Folder 117)
  - Fiering, Henry (Box 24, Folder 118)
  - Fitzpatrick, Michael (see also District 6) (Box 24, Folder 119)
  - Fitzpatrick, Thomas (see also District 6) (Box 24, Folder 120)
  - Flynn, Jerry: Local 201 (Box 24, Folder 121)
  - Folkes, Charles (Box 24, Folder 122)
  - Foner, Moe: Local 1199 (Box 24, Folder 123)
  - Ford, Theodore: Local 119 (Box 24, Folder 124)
  - Foreman, Clark (Box 24, Folder 125)
  - Frazier, Siles: Local 103 President (Box 24, Folder 126)
  - Gaeth, Arthur (Box 24, Folder 127)
  - Gallagher: Local 407 (Box 24, Folder 128)
  - Garfield, Art (Box 24, Folder 129)
  - Garry, James: District 4 (Box 24, Folder 130)
  - Gaul, Walter (Box 24, Folder 131)
  - Geiser, Carl (Box 24, Folder 132)
  - Geisz, Henry (Box 24, Folder 133)
  - Geraneo, Joseph (Box 24, Folder 134)
  - Gilbert, Sidney: Local 1227 (Box 24, Folder 135)
  - Gillingham, Mary: Local 701 (Box 24, Folder 136)
  - Goetz, Fred: News Columnist (Box 24, Folder 137)
  - Gojack, John (Box 24, Folder 138)
  - Golatta, Frances: Local 430 (Box 24, Folder 139)
  - Glavin, Denis (Box 24, Folder 140)
  - Grabinski, Walter: Local 164 F (Box 24, Folder 141)
  - Gruenberg, Lillian (Box 24, Folder 142)
  - Gyler, Sgt. Emanuel: Local 1227 (Box 24, Folder 143)
  - Habscmidt, J.: Local 107 F (Box 24, Folder 144)
  - Hall, T.E.: Local 610 (Box 24, Folder 145)
  - Hanley, Joseph: Local 108 President (Box 24, Folder 146)
  - Hannigan, Arthur: Local 262 (Box 24, Folder 147)
  - Harley, Hugh (Box 24, Folder 148)
  - Harris, Don: District 8 President (Box 24, Folder 149)
  - Harris, George: District 5 Secretary Treasurer (Box 24, Folder 150)
  - Hart, James B.: Field Organizer (Box 24, Folder 151)
  - Hartnett (Box 24, Folder 152)
  - Haug, Fred: Local 707 (Box 24, Folder 153)
  - Hebble, Vernon: Local 924 President (Box 24, Folder 154)
  - Hein, Gus: Local 327 (Box 24, Folder 155)
  - Helfand, Max and Ellie: District 1 (Box 24, Folder 156)
  - Hicks, Henry: Local 218 (Box 24, Folder 157)
  - Hodges, Bill: Local 301 (Box 24, Folder 158)
  - Holmes, John J.: Field Organizer (Box 24, Folder 159)
  - Houchins, Edward: Local 119 (Box 24, Folder 160)
  - Hovis, John (Box 32, Folder 43)
  - Hughes, Ed (Box 24, Folder 161)
  - Hupman, Red (Box 24, Folder 162)
  - Iacovangelo, Michael: Local 211 (Box 24, Folder 163)
  - Iovenelli, Sadie: Local 301 (Box 24, Folder 164)
  - Jackson, Clarence: District 5 President (Box 24, Folder 165)
  - Jacquot, Francis: Local 255 (Box 24, Folder 166)
  - Jandreau, Leonard: Business Agent (Box 24, Folder 167)
  - Jimenez, Margarita (Box 24, Folder 168)
  - Jimenez, Michael (Box 24, Folder 169)
  - Jividen, Pearl: District 7 President (Box 24, Folder 170)
  - Johnson, David (Box 24, Folder 171)
  - Johnson, Manning: Labor Spy (Box 24, Folder 172)
  - Jones, Philip (Box 24, Folder 173)
  - Joyce, Hugh: Local 201 (Box 24, Folder 174)
  - Julianelle, Joseph (Box 24, Folder 175)
  - Jurich, Joseph: Local 610 Chief Steward (Box 24, Folder 176)
  - Kaiser, Mary: Local 634 (Box 24, Folder 177)
  - Kane, James M. (Box 24, Folder 178)
  - Kaplan, Harry: Field Organizer (Box 24, Folder 179)
  - Karpa, Michael: Local 1114 (Box 24, Folder 180)
  - Keller, Charles: Field Organizer (Box 24, Folder 181)
  - Kelly, Arnold: Local 1001 (Box 24, Folder 182)
  - Kelly, Charles: Local 957 (Box 24, Folder 183)
  - Kelly, Fred: Local 201 (Box 24, Folder 184)
  - Kelly, William: Local 301 (Box 24, Folder 185)
  - Kimball, Beatrice: Local 201 (Box 24, Folder 186)
  - Kimmel, Louis: District 8 (Box 24, Folder 187)
  - King, Louis: District 3 President (Box 24, Folder 188)
  - Kirkendall, K.M. (Box 24, Folder 189)
  - Kirkland, Thomas: Local 1012 (Box 24, Folder 190)
  - Kirkwood, Robert: Director of Organization (Box 24, Folder 191)
  - Kisby, Helen (Box 24, Folder 192)
  - Klinger, Nelson (Box 24, Folder 193)
  - Klinesmith, Charles: Local 634 (Box 24, Folder 194)
  - Kochert, Rieta: Local 910 (Box 24, Folder 195)
  - Kokolus, Paul (Box 24, Folder 196)
  - Komuves, Emil: Local 475 (Box 24, Folder 197)
  - Kornfedder, Joseph Zack: Labor Spy (Box 24, Folder 198)
  - Koteles, Angela (Box 24, Folder 199)
  - Kozma, William: Local 758 (Box 24, Folder 200)
  - Krames, Sol: Local 1225 (Box 24, Folder 201)
  - Kres, Joseph: District 7 (Box 24, Folder 202)
  - Krupnick, Doris and Catherine (Box 24, Folder 203)
  - Kuschell, Willard: Local 301 (Box 24, Folder 204)
  - Krug, George: Local 1105 (Box 24, Folder 205)
  - Lambiase, Carol (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - LaRouche, Lyndon H. (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Leroy, Gaylord (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Leto, John: Local 103 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Levy, Mark: Field Organizer (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Lewis, Robert: General Committee (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Lieberman, William: Local 202 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Linehan, Jeremiah: Local 201 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Linsley, Richard: International Representative (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Livingston, David: District 65 Secretary Treasurer (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Logsdon, Robert: District 8 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Loney, Stanley: Local 617 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Loock, Fred F.: Local 1111 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Lord, Ivan: Local 254 President (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Lottman, Walter: Local 768 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Lowell, Charles: Local 205 President (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Lugo, Jose: Local 404 Business Agent (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Lustig, James (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Lynch, Richard (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Lyons, Daniel: Local 158 President (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - MacCormick, Alex: Local 218 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Malkin, Maurice: Informer (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Mamber, Philip: District 2 President (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Mangino, Joseph: Local 301 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Marcantoni, Vita (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Marcum, Charles: Local 754 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Marguriet, Daniel: District 6 President (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Marinaccio, Michael: Local 211 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Markland, Clem: District 7 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Markley, Alex: Field Organizer (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Marricaceo, Michael: Local 211 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Martin, Sandra: Local 1412 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Martinson, H.M.: Local 1412 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Marzani, Carl (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Massa, Leon: Local 259 Trustee (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Massan, Richard: District 11 Field Organizer (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Mastriani, William: Local 301 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Matthews, Edward (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Mattia, Mary: District 4 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Matuson, Harvey: Informer (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Mauseth, William: District 11 (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Mazzei, Joseph: Labor Spy (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - McAfee, Samuel (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - McAvoy, Clifford (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - McCartney, Marguerite (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - McConnell, J.W.: Local 825 President (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - McDaniel, Mary: District 10 President (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - McLeigh, James (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - McNeil, Allan (Box 25, Folder 49)
  - McWilliams, Carey (Box 25, Folder 50)
  - Mensch, Helen (Box 25, Folder 51)
  - Metcalfe, Jack (See also District 6) (Box 25, Folder 52)
  - Mihalick, Steven (Curley) (Box 25, Folder 53)